<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="perm_send">SEND SMS</string>
    <string name="permdescr_send">This allows an app to send SMS messages using Super Duper SMS Manager</string>
    
    <string name="sdmmChangeDefSmsTitleTxt">Set \"Super Duper Messaging Manager\" As The Default SMS App</string>
    <string name="sdmmChangeDefSmsDescrTxt">BETA: Some apps will work even when SDMM is *not* the default messaging app.
        \n\nTo enable \"Super Duper SMS\" most messaging and features you must set it as your default SMS app.
        </string>
    <string name="sdmmChangeDefSmsChangeTxt">Go Now</string>
    <string name="sdmmChangeDefSmsNoChangeTxt">No Thanks</string>
    
	<string name="instKitKatFoundWarningTitle">This Android Version Requires \"Super Duper Messaging Manager\"</string>
	<string name="instKitKatFoundWarningDescr">Super Duper Messaging Manager is required for this app to work properly on this version of Android.
	    \n\nAndroid KitKat and Lollipop completely change the way that text messaging works. 
	    Without a manager app, this app will not work properly.
	    \n\nHowever, installing and using Super Duper Messaging Manager (SDMM) should be easy! Give it a try! 
		\n\nPlease contact us if you have questions.</string>
	<string name="instKitKatFoundWarningInstall">Go To Market</string>
	<string name="instKitKatFoundWarningMoreInfo">No Thanks</string>
			
	<string name="sdmmVerifiedTitle">\"Super Duper Messaging Manager\" Verified</string>
	<string name="sdmmVerifiedDescr">Super Duper Messaging Manager is installed and is working properly.
	    \n\nThanks and please contact us with problems or questions.
		</string>
	<string name="sdmmVerifiedDone">Done</string>
			
	<string name="sdmmLaunchTitleTxt">Make \"Super Duper Messaging Manager\" Your Default SMS</string>
    <string name="sdmmLaunchDescrTxt">Please set \"Super Duper SMS\" as your default SMS app.</string>
    <string name="sdmmLaunchTxt">Go Now</string>
    <string name="sdmmLaunchNoLaunchTxt">Cancel</string>

    <string name="initLocationTitleTxt">Setup Notifications
        \nfor Super Duper</string>
    <string name="initListenerInstructionsLblTxt">\"Super Duper Messaging Manager (SDMM)\" needs access to notifications.</string>
    <string name="initListenerInstructionsLblTxt2">Select \"Setup Now\" then please check the box next to \"SuperDuper Messaging Service\"!</string>
    <string name="initListenerContinueBtnTxt">Setup Now</string>
    <string name="initListenerCancelBtnTxt">Cancel</string>
</resources>